var quiz = [

{
	"question" : "BAE",
	"correctanswer": "BABY",
	"answer2": "POOP",
	"answer3": "BACON AND EGGS",
	"answer4": "CRUSH",

},

{

	"question" : "FIRE",
	"correctanswer": "INCREDIBLE",
	"answer2": "HELL",
	"answer3": "ACTUAL FIRE",
	"answer4": "HOT IN TEMPERATURE",
},

{

	"question" : "LIT",
	"correctanswer": "TURNED UP",
	"answer2": "LIGHTNING",
	"answer3": "ALL GOOD",
	"answer4": "INTOXICATED",
},

{

	"question" : "DEAD",
	"correctanswer": "HILARIOUS",
	"answer2": "NOT PHYSICALLY ALIVE",
	"answer3": "SUCKS",
	"answer4": "DONE",
},

{

	"question" : "CANCELLED",
	"correctanswer": "GET LOST",
	"answer2": "TOO YOUNG",
	"answer3": "TERRIFYING",
	"answer4": "NO LONGER PLANNED",
},

{

	"question" : "LOW-KEY",
	"correctanswer": "KINDA",
	"answer2": "HIGHKEY",
	"answer3": "NOT IMPORTANT",
	"answer4": "CLOSE TO THE GROUND",
},

{

	"question" : "SUS",
	"correctanswer": "SUSPICIOUS",
	"answer2": "SUSAN",
	"answer3": "SUSTAIN",
	"answer4": "A FLAW",
},

{

	"question" : "PREACH",
	"correctanswer": "AMEN TO THAT",
	"answer2": "THATS COOL",
	"answer3": "YES",
	"answer4": "KEEP GOING",
},

{

	"question" : "BOUNCE",
	"correctanswer": "TO LEAVE",
	"answer2": "TO PHYSICALLY JUMP",
	"answer3": "SPUNK",
	"answer4": "BOUNCY",
},

{

	"question" : "OOF",
	"correctanswer": "JEEZ",
	"answer2": "MISSPELLING OF OAF",
	"answer3": "GOOD",
	"answer4": "YES",
},

{

	"question" : "SLAY",
	"correctanswer": "KILLED IT",
	"answer2": "WISE",
	"answer3": "GREAT",
	"answer4": "LOVE IT",
},

]












